Hello you're with us.
Welcome to the first among a series of tutorials to get you started with programming language.
This will be a short session to help you with the basics like the features of the Python language and
how to get them to work on the machine.
With that go and let's get into your first lesson on Batan.
The session goes the following topics introduction to Python the fetus and setting up by an all new
machine.
Introduction to the Biden programming language was developed in the late 80s.
And it was designed from a number of other programming languages like C C++ small dog and a few others.
It is a high level interpreter object oriented programming language.
Well that's quite a few heavy terminology isn't a but well we are here to break things down for you.
The high level programming language is one that may use or disclose to natural human language or contained
elements from natural language thus making the programs simpler as an example.
The word friend might indeed be meaningful to a high level programming language
and interpreted language enables you to run the exact code you wrote without having to rely on someone
else to convert your code into a language spoken by your computer with just the zeros and ones someone
else being a compiler.
In most cases mortarboard compilers later
in object oriented programming language treats everything like real world objects or go up in object
oriented terms is an object and employ as an object.
Both of these know how to get stuff done like drive or work.
You write code to ask these objects to get the stuff done.
This is a pretty simplified explanation and made some really silly for a non beginner.
Our intention is to get all the complexity out at the beginning and we'll definitely be diving deep
into these concepts a little way later.
Moving on to features Bitin is simple.
Which means it is easy to learn and read.
Now we touched on the word trend a while ago when we discussed high level languages.
The word print does indeed have a meaning in python.
No that's your first example.
The word print followed by some text within court lets you get these text appear on the screen.
We shot them all for you
the word friend told by a few text
within quotes.
And hit enter.
We can see the text blowpipe them printed on the screen simply isn't it
moving on to the next feature that is portability
Peyton can run on very many hardware platforms and isn't restricted to being used in a single type of
machine.
It works like a charm on huge commercial enterprise so to a handheld device all of these do it being
open source which is the third feature by open source we mean anybody with enough knowledge can contribute
to the source code and make language better by sharing and making changes to the code.
There is a strong community backing pikemen that helps keep it Mazan strong.
Every day we shall touch on the word nice to go with the final feature on our list.
That is Lively's a huge collection of libraries in Python takes your work off from your shoulders since
they help you write that's called white and has tons of these written by people in the white community
who are way smarter than me.
It's more into how we set up the Python programming language on our machines.
On Macs like the one we're using now you are good to go by typing in the word byte in after finding
a diplomatic.
Now we'll follow this up with a simple exercise to demonstrate this concept.
It does begin by taking the permanent
to begin with and a vital interpreter.
I type in Python and press and the I mean to the Python interpreter and in order to start reading my
first program that is I want to print the text along.
I type in print followed by a word in quotes and press ENTER Kenzi the word hello world printed on the
screen.
Moving on
mostly gets distribution's followed the same procedure so we have that covered as well.
Addition to that we have a few that in Macs and Linux Biden 2.10 comes preinstalled.
But for Windows you have an additional work.
The Windows users are tuned in can listen to what you see on your screen and download the 32 bit on
the 64 bit installers with Jim Baker of rest of the procedures.
We have a screen grab from the website and you'll have to specifically install either of the two options
listed within the rectangular box.
With that we are wrapping up the first session.
We hope we got you excited about them and we look forward to meeting you the next day.
Until then it's goodbye.