Is today I'll take you to introduction to programming language and Python programming language.
So before we get to know about Python programming language what actually is a programming language.
Any ideas.
OK.
Helio a programming language is nothing but a language which is used to communicate with the computer
which is nothing but the machine there many programming languages available in the market like Java
C++ C ash Perl dot net acceptance and Python is one among them is Python is emerging as as popular day
by day because of its simplicity and easy to use and easy to learn and also begin able to learn it in
a short period of time and beginning with the goal in a short period of time.
All right.
Basically the languages I mean the programming languages are categorized into two depths.
One is independent languages and one is compiling languages.
Lex Noye board interpreter language.
All right so what I actually mean by interpretation
interpretation is a process of executing a program line by line.
It means one statement at a time that it had run.
So this was in the order which leaves you a programming code line by line and exit using that again
at runtime in a language that can be understand by the machine.
So this was your final execution.
All right.
So interpreter is the one which does this task of executing your code line by line.
So this is all about independent what I actually mean by compiler.
Or the combination language.
All right so compulsion is nothing but the process of conducting the type programming called you have
written in a language that can be understood by the computer which is nothing but in the form of zero
Gummo Once a machine can able to understand a language which is binary that is zero.
So this is all that that can be understood by the Conchobar and is a Final Exit exhiliration called
data that a computer can able to understand.
So this is all about ambulation.
So compilers and interpreters are the two important topics that can be related to programming language
and some of the compiler languages or Java C++ dot net C ash etc. and some of interpretor languages
are by then Ruby BHB ball etc..
All right.
So let's come to bite.
So what does Biden Biden is an interpreter.
High-Level object oriented programming languages language which is very easy to look
so bite and that are is a main official Web site of the Biden where you have tons of material.
And you know a notion of bidon topics.
So this Web site contains the Biden software with the various Russians.
So from downloads link you've been able to see there are various versions of Biden's software available
to download for different options of operating systems.
So you can able to see that you've been able to download bidon software for Linux and Mac and other
operating systems.
Byte tree was a recent release that has many new futures and functionalities and and 2.7 was most widely
used and popular.
So before you get you get familiar with Python describer use this pipe and 2.7
so.
So that's all you guys.
This is a direction of bite and programming language and also introduction to programming language.
In our next tutorials Let's.
Let's let's get in deep byte and like this.
I mean the data Daibes syntax etc..
Thank you yes.