Hi everyone let's get started.
But before diving into Python programming let's decide which ideally we will use for college.
There are several ideas like Nadine's by jam Jupiter in sublime wishes to your core Xandra.
So let's select one from the 10 best ideas for Python programmers and I'm going to select the main one
sublime extreme discipline picks three is one of the most powerful crossplatform like we gaudily do
is do that and for beginners it is the best idea to use.
So let's in-style it and before.
I want to show you my system configuration.
I'm using elementarily 64 bit Windu right now and all installations will be done based on this configuration.
Select install synoptic package manager first.
It will help you to download all the related files over Bowdler package simultaneously.
So since I have installed synoptic package banish'd you let's go to an IP package manager and install
Sublette and in the search box just type for sublight and it will list all the related items of subline
baggage and just pick one up label.
And again this Uplay button will not be files for us.
And before doing all these delusions and downloads and all.
Just make sure that you are connected to the Internet.
Saw this in Optik package manager have done its job.
So we have installed some blame you know system and the selection of the synoptic package manager or
software sender for downloading bobos is up to you.
You can select any one from this and Cinetic package manager is simpler than software Sandu I think
and it's completely free.
You can select anyone according to your convenience.
So let's go to these subline decks right now.
This is the sublime text of sublime ID.
And I have selected by the language.
And here we can see all the languages that suf ordered by Sublime Text.
And since we are calling in then we are selecting by then and are always here in the right cold.
In the upper position we can see something.
This is nothing but just the mini map.
Many map shows all the codes in the miniature forms that we are having in this country.
That's it.
And if that is disturbing you then just go to the view and hide it.
And we have got many other options on here.
File options.
New File Open file open folder Ixo drop options.
I don't and using all these options and this is all we can do many things like the programming and this
ID in Python will be standard by the next two words.
So that's all for now.
Keep watching
and thank.