Hello guys you'll begin to know what programming language and fighting in Israel will implement or exiguous
in Python healable.
Hope you have Biden installed on your computer from this link from the official Python web site.
Hope you have.
You're using two pencil and a lot of the motion.
You're really convenient.
All right.
In Python we're going to go into in two ways.
One is by using the interpreter and one is by using the Python scripts.
Basically a file is called Blyton's to bite and module if it's ends with Dot people.
It means python files ends with an extension of God.
But but if you have a very large lot of code to be executed it's better to write a script with got extension
and exit.
Vigeland All right.
So last fall let let's implement a simple hello world program by using the interpreter.
Open the domina.
I have already opened it and the not entered into by an interpreter.
How we can do that simple just type it down without any input arguments to it and present the that's
all.
Now you are in the Biden interview.
These three arrow marks shows you that tells you that you entered into by an interpreter.
And now we can execute the code we want here.
So let's implement a simple by Dunhills Broga
room that top that Tolland by Biden to bring up the exiguous as it will help what.
So let's let's understand what this is all print.
What has been printed is nothing but by done building function that prints any data from byte and program
and hellebore is a string.
So the building function and the string combines and formed and formed the Biden program.
So this is all about a simple hello world program in Python.
We can also implement this by then Hellawell program using byte scripts on modules as we have discussed.
And the second point is so let's implement this Helliwell program using scaped
exeat don't have speak create a Biden fight Autumn what one you
have created by done more with an extension of Darbyville that now.
No it was a blackflies and let's write something or some program.
This was seen as the one having been injured on the tiny know we have no single program no hope and
hoping to get it.
Go to Domina use the word Biden and find him.
There you go.
You've been able to see the string Hello all that we have been dead from the Bidens good.
That's all in Biden.
So able to execute our programs in two ways.
One is independent and one is by scripts.
Let's do some meaningful.
When this hello world string but using some functions don't worry about disfunctions datatype etc. We'll
be getting too deep with these topics.
No extra problems for now.
Let's bring this hello world using Python function.
All right.
We have written a simple function called Hello world and inside that we are building the word hello
world and def is nothing but the negation in by Biden which indicates that this was a function.
And finally we are calling this function to bring this hellova.
Let's exiguous this file from Domina
same as we did before.
Did you will you've been able to see the string hello world that we are hoping that you have executed
or that you have been Dinda to print that from.
Function
All right.
So we have seen of executing this problem in the builder and also to bite on scripts.
There are many ways to implement or to exit this program using functions with taking different arguments
etc..
So in the next two tutorial will know something.
Something in DB like datatypes syntax etc..
That's all for this tutorial guys.
See the next tutorial.
Thank you very much.